(Mrs Cooper:)Well, I love you, too.
(Mrs Cooper:)My little bowl
of lion chow.
(Dr Hofstadter:)So, have you and Penny
set a wedding date?
(Leonard:)No, we're kind of
taking it slow.
(Dr Hofstadter:)I see.
(Leonard:)What does that mean?
(Dr Hofstadter:)You've been on and off with
this woman for seven years
(Dr Hofstadter:)and engaged for one year.
(Dr Hofstadter:)One has to wonder
if there's a problem.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Are you having
satisfactory intercourse?
(Leonard:)Yes, Mother.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Only satisfactory.
I see.
(Leonard:)I change my answer.
It-it's amazing.
It's hot.
(Leonard:)We can barely keep our
hands off each other.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Seems odd to try
and impress your mother
(Dr Hofstadter:)with your
sexual prowess.
(Dr Hofstadter:)But then, you always did have
that unresolved Oedipal complex.